iblog.com 2017-05-17

# Please find our Privacy Policy Here | iBLOG | iBlog

Please find our  **[Terms of Service](http://iblog.com/terms-of-service/ "Terms Of Service")**  here.

This IBlog Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) discloses the privacy practices for us at IBlog.com (“IBlog”) and how we treat the information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of website products and services. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that IBlog does not own or control or to people that IBlog does not employ or manage. By visiting this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access our website.

**1\. Information Collected**

IBlog collects information from users at different points on its website. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Information we collect includes:

(a) Personally Identifiable Information. This includes information that can directly identify an individual, such as an individual’s name, mailing address, phone number and/or email address. In order to use services on this website, a user must create an account. During the account creation process, a user must provide Personally Identifiable Information so that we can stay in touch with our users. This information is also used to fulfill the duties required of our requested services. To help prevent fraudulent sign ups, we may also ask a user to provide financial information (e.g. credit card). This information may also be used for billing purposes, with the help of our business partner.

(b) IP addresses. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information.

(c) Cookies and Web Beacons. Internet browsers have a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on a user’s computer hard drive that contains information about that user. Web beacons, also called “web bugs,” “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs” may be used in combination with cookies. A Web beacon is typically a small graphic image on a website that is also used to collect information about a user (not including your name, address, email address or phone number). If a user rejects the cookie and/or modifies their browser settings to prevent / turn off cookies (which should also prevent web beacons from tracking a user’s activities on the website), the user may still use our website. The only drawback to this is that the user may be limited in some areas of our website. Cookies and web beacons can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website. Some of our business partners use cookies and/or web beacons on our website (e.g. advertisers); however, we have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons.

(d) Third Party Advertisers. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements when you visit our website or use our services. Third-party companies may also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

(e) Information from Third Parties. In certain circumstances, in order for our website to properly fulfill its obligation to our users, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we collect pursuant to this Privacy Policy with information from third party sources.

**2\. How Information Collected Is Used**

We will not knowingly use information collected on this website in ways different from what is disclosed in the Privacy Policy that is currently in effect.

(a) Demographic Information. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. The aggregated demographic information is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information that can identify any individual person.

(b) Communicating with Our Users. We use Personally Identifiable Information (such as a user’s name, telephone number and/or email address) to communicate with that specific user when they have questions, concerns or comments about their account or the services that we provide. If a user contacts us, we may or may not delete the user’s emails or voicemails to us.

(c) Information Shared With Third Parties. We share information with third parties in order to give our customers access to a great variety of services. Specifically, we may do the following:

(i) Use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not use Personally Identifiable Information for any use other than credit card processing; however, we will not be responsible or liable for use of the information required by credit card companies in contravention of their policies, contractual obligations, applicable laws or general good business procedures;

(ii) Partner with third parties who provide services to our users. When the user signs up for or agrees to receive a specific service provided by the third party, we share the information that is needed for the third party to provide the services; and

(iii) Share your Personally Identifiable Information with other entities that are owned by IBlog, that own IBlog, or have some sort of corporate ownership relationship with IBlog.

(d) Addressing Legal Issues. We provide Personally Identifiable Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share Personally Identifiable Information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IBlog’s terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.

(e) Sale or Transfer of IBlog. If all or a portion of IBlog is transferred, sold, merged, ceases operations, goes bankrupt, or is otherwise involved in a transaction where the ownership or management of IBlog is changed (individually or collectively, a “Transaction”) then your Personally Identifiable Information or other user information may be transferred or assigned to a third party as part of the Transaction.

**3\. Usage by Children Under Age 18**

This website is not intended for use by anyone under the age of eighteen (18), and any individual under such age should not provide us with Personally Identifiable Information. We do not knowingly contact, market to, solicit, collect or use Personally Identifiable Information from or about any individual under the age of 18. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 18. If we are notified that we have personal information regarding a person under the age of 18, as soon as we reasonably verify the information, we will either obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from the account and/or service. However, the information may remain on a log in our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under the age of 18, please do so by emailing us at: Privacy [at] IBlog.com.

**4\. Communications from IBlog**

(a) Welcome Emails and Marketing Correspondence. We send a account activation email to the email address associated with the account a user has created to verify the user’s. This process is designed to prevent e-mail addresses from being used without permission in the creation of an IBlog account. Established users may occasionally receive marketing material from IBlog on products and services provided by IBlog and/or IBlog’s third party partners.

(b) Website and Service Updates. We send the user website and service announcement updates. Users are not permitted to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the website and/or service. We may communicate with users to provide services that users request or to discuss issues relating to their account.

(c) Contests. From time-to-time our website may request information from users via contests. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and, as such, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

**5\. Correcting/Updating Personal Information**

Users must provide accurate and correct contact information (e.g. name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number) for their user account. If a user’s Personally Identifiable Information changes (such as a zip code), they may correct and/or update such information from within their account. If further assistance is needed, please send an email to Privacy [at] IBlog.com.

**6\. Opting Out**

Users are provided an opportunity to “opt-out” of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the services they request. Users who no longer wish to receive certain marketing materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying and typing “unsubscribe” in the subject line in the email or by sending an email request to Privacy [at] IBlog.com .  If you opt out, we may still send you certain types of communications, such as updates for your services, transactional or legal notification emails, and we may respond to requests from you by email.

We do not respond to “do not track” signals, if any, being sent from your browser. Furthermore, we may permit select third parties to collect non-personal information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you use IBlog. If you would like to opt-out of any of the technologies that we and/or our third parties employ to collect your information via IBlog (e.g. cookies), you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device permits. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about your browser settings and how to handle cookies. For more information on third-party advertising-related cookies and how to exercise your choice to opt-out of them, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices and/or www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**7\. Account Termination**

If your IBlog account is terminated or cancelled (regardless of whether it was voluntary) all of your Personally Identifiable Information will remain on our servers. Upon receipt of a written request to remove personal data, we will retain some of your information in order to prevent fraud, collect fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our other policies, address contractual issues, contact you for future marketing or promotional purposes, and comply with legal requirements. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, your account will be deactivated from our active, registered user database, and will only be available to select personnel.

**8\. Links to Third Party Websites**

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website. You are responsible for reviewing the privacy policy of each and every website you visit to determine the handling of your Personally Identifiable Information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by IBlog’s website.

**9\. Security**

Users are required to keep their account passwords confidential and to not share this information with others. If you choose to reveal or share your password and IBlog account name, we are unable to guarantee the security of your account. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to Privacy [at] IBlog.com.

**10\. Privacy Policy Changes**

From time to time, we may choose to modify this Privacy Policy. If we make minor changes to this Privacy Policy, the changes will be immediately effective upon posting the revised Privacy Policy to the website. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use or collect your Personally Identifiable Information, all amended terms shall automatically be effective ten (10) days after they are initially posted on the site. The date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy is the date that the Privacy Policy is effective. You are responsible for periodically checking our Privacy Policy for any modifications. Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will only be applicable to disputes arising, or arising out of events occurring, after the effective date of such Privacy Policy. You agree that you will continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy, however and whenever it is modified, if you continue to use IBlog website after the modifications are effective.

**11\. Privacy Policy Concerns or Questions**

If you have any concern about privacy at IBlog, please send us a thorough description to Privacy [at] IBlog.com, and we will try to resolve it.
